ני 咩?
個 咩?
How come someone licked it?
怎麼有人舔過呢?
Give some!
畀啲!
Ah you hell!
啊你佢地!
I asked Ah Sinni...
我問阿Sinni...
He appreciates where we finally spent the most?!
佢最欣賞我哋finally邊過啊 ?!
As for Sinni, it's like my two side boys, okay?
Sinni呢,係我二隻邊仔似嘅, 好嗎?
OK!
好啊!
Brother Shu, one word, the fate is stable and pure, Brother Shu!
書兄話一言,緣化定而淨,書兄!
It's early, brother!
早咗啊,師兄!
Ximi, I, I like to set it, myself.
係咪,我,我鍾意擺定啊,我自己
I want to say brother, why are you here?
我就想說師兄,點解係你喺度嘅?
Gao Ning type microphone?
高檸係咪?
Tall, beautiful, fat again!
又高左,又靚左,又肥左喎!
By the way, Gao Ning is going to take care of your body today and go to the hospital for treatment.
話說啦,高檸係今日身體保養, 去生病療
So let's replace him...
所以就我哋頂替佢喇.
Also, I know you guys come to Namco to shoot, I want to go to Namco too.
另外,我就知道你哋嚟Namco拍 嘢, 我都好想去Namco玩喇,
So we came to Namco.
所以我哋嚟Namco嚟喇.
Because our episode is sponsored by Namco!
因為我哋今集係由Namco贊助 嘅!
Yes, we are about to have a series of competitions inside...
係喇,我哋即將係裏面進行一連串嘅 比賽喇.
Hey, we've been grouped, right?
咦,我哋已經分好組囉,係咪?
There is a mistake!
有錯喎!
we are...
我哋係...
Student Union!
學生會!
We are the four most outstanding students you have selected...
我哋就係你哋選出嚟最優秀嘅四位學 生喇.
It doesn't seem to vote, are not back.
好似唔會投票,都係冇返到.
I choose your opponents...
我選你哋嘅對手.
What did you do to choose my opponent?
你做咩事選我對手啊?
Why did you choose my opponent?
你做咩選我對手啊?
I got it!
我得啦!
Yes, lick your hands right now...
係呀,即刻舔埋你哋隻手先喇.
I am a recipient of the Financial Step Award.
我係財政步步獎.
Tong Xiaotongla.
同曉彤喇.
I'm the worst in the school...
全學校最壞就係我喇.
I'm with Xiaotong.
我同曉彤.
I can't walk away...
無得步走.
You are on your body too...
你都上咗身咁.
I am the winner of Bubu Award.
我係空落步步獎.
Hsiao-tung and I are in peace...
我同曉彤係和喎.
Nine things, nine things.
九樣九樣.
Ok, I'm Ka-lai-ying Peng, the clerk...
好喇,我係文書嘅彭嘉麗英啊.
Order it?
點呀?
Pang Ka-lai-ying, so I can guess who will be next...
彭嘉麗英,咁我估到下一個係邊個 喇.
I am the president of the student union, Chairman Zhu.
我係學生會主席,朱主席.
This is Chairman Zhu.
係朱主席啦.
You said it's not easy...
你就講唔容易喎.
I'm just trying my best...
我都係盡力咋喎.
Never like to be alone.
從不喜歡孤單一個.
It's a pity that I am alone.
可惜偏偏孤獨一個.
I'm not...enough, okay?
我不...夠啦好嗎?
Let's go south to China Southern Airlines.
我哋去南航南上.
My name is John, and my name is Guan Yannuo.
我係阿John,我係管彥諾.
Wood flute, Tenai.
木同笛,手直.
Hands straight.
手直.
Thank you, thank you.
多謝你,多謝你.
I'm scared, I was really scared...
我好驚,我頭先真係好驚.
I'm a beetroot from the dragon hair family...
我係龍毛系嘅紅菜頭.
why is it so tight
做咩咁緊呀?
I got some beets and dyed my hair.
我中咗啲紅菜頭,跟住染咗啲頭髮.
Because what identity we are waiting for.
因為我哋等緊嗰件咩身份嘛.
What exactly is beetroot?
紅 菜頭究竟係乜嘢嚟嘅呢?
Beetroot is my name...
紅菜頭就係我個朵.
I am a fortune teller at the Astrology Society.
我係占星學會嘅占卜佬.
Fortune teller, tell me if I won or lost today...
占卜佬咁咪講吓我今日贏定輸.
Lose?
輸呀?
Win.
贏呀.
I'm the most obedient in the school.
我係全學校最乖嘅,攝三尺埋條胎入 去嘅.
President of the Xiangqi Society and International Chess Society.
象棋學會,國際象棋學會商會長.
My name is Cheng Shuang.
我叫程雙.
Cheng Shuang.
程雙.
Wow, she's been bandaged for a long time...
嘩,佢紮咗好耐啦.
So you thought you pressed me...
咁你諗住壓咗我.
My name is Cheng Shuang.
我叫程雙.
Well, let’s not talk so much.
好啦,唔好講咁多啦.
Let's go into Namco and play right away.
我哋即刻入去Namco度玩啦.
"Happy Solutions".
快樂解數.
Check out the rules of the game now...
即刻睇下遊戲規則啦.
Clamp the doll to pass three levels.
夾公仔過三關.
The two teams need to pin out the dolls in the pinball machine...
兩隊需要喺夾公仔機內夾出公仔.
And throw it into the Full Line circle to complete the three-level competition.
並拋到Full Line圈內進行 過三關比賽.
The team that is the fastest to connect three laps into a line wins...
最快將三個圈連成一線嘅隊伍為之勝 出.
If the doll is thrown out of the circle, or thrown into the dominant Full Line circle.
如果公仔被拋出圈外,或者拋到以霸 佔嘅Full Line圈內,
will be deemed invalid.
則視為無效.
The game version looks like this...
遊戲版本就係咁樣啦.
On behalf of the Namco boys, we will definitely win yours...
我代表Namco男生講,我哋一定 會贏你哋嘅.
And we only need to fold three.
同埋我哋只需要夾三個就搞掂.
The whole bunch of little bugs are losing...
成班小蟲都係輸啦.
Wow, so weak, so weak.
嘩,好弱,好弱.
The student union can help.
學生會幫幫忙啦.
Our students will cancel your clubs.
我哋學生會取消你哋啲學會.
You will never be able to catch the debt period again...
你哋以後都冇得再捉帳期.
You can't buy our beard powder...
你哋唔可以買我哋嘅鬚粉.
In short, the four of us will win you three.
總之我哋四個都會贏你三個啦.
Why the three of us?
點解我哋三個?
Lost the throne.
敗位啦.
Sorry, there's another one here, can't see it...
Sorry,仲有一個喺度, 睇唔到.
So let's get started right away.
咁我哋即刻開始啦.
Three pills in one foot for you to see...
一腳夾三粒俾你睇.
Four's butts are awesome...
四個嘅屁股好正.
I want to kick him...
好想踢佢一腳.
No please.
唔好啦.
3,2,1,start.
3,2,1,開始.
Fold the middle one first, the middle one first...
夾中間嗰粒先,中間嗰粒先.
just right
啱啱好.
Is it powerful enough?
夠唔夠力啊?
Enough, enough, enough.
夠呀夠呀夠呀.
hurry up
快啲上呀.
may not work may not work
未必得嘅未必得.
You guys failed.
你哋失敗咗.
continue continue continue.
繼續繼續繼續.
The whole whole.
整個整個.
You save, you save.
你度你度.
middle, middle, middle.
中間,中間,中間.
ah!
呀!
It’s elastic!
有彈力呀!
Has elasticity!
有彈力!
Are you wearing glasses?
你係咪眼鏡呀?
No lenses?
冇鏡片呀?
Yes yes, we pretend to be sons...
係呀係呀,我哋扮仔呀.
The past, the right just...
前啲前事,啱啲啱啱.
Be careful not to get into their mouths, their mouths are hard...
小心唔好對入咗佢哋嘅口呀, 佢哋嘅口好硬呀.
OK, OK, OK, OK.
係呀,OK,OK,OK.
Let's go!
Let's go!
Don't get into it, oops, into the mouth...
唔好入到佢,哎呀,入左個口呀.
We really have not succeeded, really have Ning Baoning, Ning give you.
我哋成功真係未到,真係有寧寶寧, 寧畀你.
Nothing, OK, OK, OK, nothing.
冇嘢呀,OK呀,OK呀,OK呀, 冇嘢.
Yes, yes, yes!
有呀,有呀,有呀!
You are tied to the wheel willow, you are tied to the wheel willow.
你係輪柳呀,你係輪柳呀.
Yes, yes, yes.
有呀,有呀,有呀.
You ignore him, ignore him...
你唔好理佢,唔好理佢.
He is a willow...
佢係輪柳呀.
Yeah!
Yeah!
Take a look, take a look.
攞個樣,攞個樣.
nothing
冇嘢呀,冇嘢呀.
Yes, yes, yes.
有呀,有呀,有呀.
Why can't one of us get along?
點解我哋一個都夾唔到呢?
Enter the strength, enter the strength, fortune box, hurry up hey...
進咗力,進咗力,占福盒,快啲啦 喂.
Hey!
Hey!
Ha ha ha ha.
哈哈哈哈.
Yeah!
Yeah!
Hello!
喂!
ah!
啊!
why are you guys so naughty
點解你哋咁犀嚟嘅?
Is it difficult to clip the edges of the fruit?
果邊好難夾啦?
Here you go, here you go!
給你,給你!
Damn blue!
藍靠!
I really can't do it today.
我今天真唔得.
I win you, look at this one of ours.
贏你啦,睇下我哋呢封咪夾到囉.
look once you came...
睇下你一嚟咗...
Yeah!
Yeah!
Yes!
Yes!
Also lose Mi BiRen Zuo Ren Zuo Ren Zuo Mi.
又輸咪比人左人左人左咪.
So cool...
好勁...
have!
有!
The only one on the left is Li!
左隻個黎!
The one on the left loses!
左隻個黎輸!
Half snake cono swag pig bang pig yeah seal it ah have yeah have yeah fried pig
半蛇 cono 掙豬呀掙豬呀 封 住佢 啊有呀有呀有 炸豬
nails jaar high jar ago Gilana intercepted his ground!
nails jaar高 jar ago Gilana 截佢地!
Cut him off!
截佢地!
Let's play together. Let's play together. Yeah, hey, hey, hey...
我地一齊玩啦 我地一齊 Yeah 喂 喂 喂喂喂...
Quick, quick!
快啲,快啲!
Touch the eyes!
觸眼!
Win if you touch it!
觸眼就贏啦!
no, sorry!
不行呀!
Come up and measure?
上嚟測下?
You guys go!
你哋走呀!
Don't pick him up either!
你亦都唔好接佢呀!
I wonder if your trick is air clamps!
我想問你哋個絕招系咪空氣夾呀!
Is that yours?
你講咁啲係咪yours呀?
Pick him up!
接佢啲呀!
Do you want to beat up some Yue Fei?
想咪揍啲岳飛呀?
Give it a try!
試下呀!
We shipped faster than it, we shipped faster than it...
我哋快過佢出貨喇,我哋快過佢出貨 喇.
Drink la drink la drink la drink la.
飲喇飲喇飲喇飲喇.
Hey how many jumps, Chu Chu, come together...
喂跳幾啊,朱朱仔一齊嚟喇.
Ok, come on, come on...
好啊,嚟喇嚟喇.
Goubu, Zhu Zhuzai.
溝步,朱朱仔.
Sorry, I can't be sincere today...
不好意思,今日唔能誠意咁呢.
He is so shitty.
他地好屎啊.
Three', six', swim.
三個',六個', swim.
flawless, carrying, d alla.
無懈,拎的,d alla.
Come on, come on, mine is okay, mine is okay, mine is okay...
嚟喇,嚟喇,我嘅都得我嘅都得我嘅 都得.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
有啊有啊有啊有啊有啊.
So nervous.
緊張啊.
Hey Pang Jiali, you are the next owner.
喂龐嘉麗你被翻下一 owners.
Please call me by my full name, Mr. Pang Jialiying, okay?
叫翻我全名龐嘉麗英先,好嗎?
3,2,1.
3,2,1.
Pang Jialiying.
龐嘉麗英.
Just the first sound.
先聲隻.
You guys are on hunger strike. It’s so funny. Beat them.
你們絕食老 好搞笑 打他們
Forest collected 20 mosquitoes from my trade. You two, look at it. Hey, hey, hey, you can't catch people.
Forest 收咗我貿易20蚊 你倆瞅住 喂 喂喂喂,唔可以捉人
Yeah, you can't catch people...
, 唔可以捉人.
Oops, whistle.
哎呀打哨啊.
No. That's not possible.
唔可以啦.
Win left.
贏左.
Goal!
Goal!
南櫫, 南櫫, 南櫫, 南櫫, 南櫫, 南櫫.
南橫,南橫,南橫,南橫,南橫, 南橫.
It's ok, it's ok, it's ok, it
It's ok, it's ok, it's ok, it
's ok.
's ok.
OK.
OK.
Try going down straight.
試下筆直個下囉.
Wow, no inventor...
嘩, 冇發明器喎.
That's how the male sex boys won the student union...
就係咁樣, 男炮男生就咁樣贏左學 生會啦.
easy.
輕鬆.
Congratulations to them...
恭喜佢哋.
Cut你budget.
Cut你budget.
I have something to say, because our shape is spherical, so we will flick fast when we flake
我有嘢想講, 因為我哋個形狀係球 體嘅, 所以撣嘅時候都會撣得快
d.
啲.
But I want to say, our cube is actually very difficult...
但 係我想講, 我哋個立方體其實 都好難.
Astrologer, tell me.
占星佬, 你講下.
Because of the hole, it needs a surface area is more.
因為個孔呢, 佢要個sur face area係多啲.
What is called service scope?
咩叫服務範圍啊.
Not a scammer.
唔中蝦人啊.
Anyway, that's how we won it...
Anyway, 我哋就係咁樣贏左 啦.
So we have won 1-0 now...
咁我哋而家就贏左1比0喇喎.
Never mind though, we give you more chances, we have three more mini-games to play.
不過唔緊要嘅, 我哋比多啲機會 你, 我哋仲有三隻小遊戲要玩.
You have a chance to catch up...
你有機會追.
Enter the second game immediately.
即刻進入第二個遊戲.
Sticker photo challenge.
貼紙相challenge.
The contestants have to fight for entry in the sticker camera...
參賽者要喺貼紙相機內爭取入鏡.
The presenter will use a different topic as a criterion each time...
主持人每次會用唔同嘅題目作為評分 標準.
Such as eyes, ears, mouth, nose.
例如眼, 耳, 口, 鼻.
As long as the contestant's part can be captured in the camera at the end, the team will gain 1 point.
只要參賽者該部位最後可以入鏡, 就可以為隊伍爭取到1分.
After 3 rounds, the team with the highest score wins...
經過3個回合之後, 最高分嘅隊伍 為之勝出.
For a while, we will enter like this...
一陣呢, 我哋會咁樣入囉.
Jumi...so how do you get better?
朱咪咧... 咁你點樣好返到?
In the underworld, he must be taking A-ju's for dumb position. Actually...
陰間呢, 一定佢係攞阿朱咪嚟啞位 啫其實.
Is Chu Mi coming?
朱咪嚟唔嚟?
already found away
已經搵走咁嚟囉.
He is holding Chu Mi.
佢係hold住朱咪.
Three girls don't care about him...
三部女仔唔使理佢.
And find something like that 30 places for me to do?
又搵啲咁嘢30位畀我做?
Will you lose to Zhu Mi?
你會輸到朱咪咩?
You win him in everything except looks...
除咗樣之外, 你所有都贏佢.
Right, I agree...
啱, 我認同.
okay then.
咁好啦.
You know astrology...
你識占星嘛.
Do you think we were the first to win or lose?
你覺得我哋第一個贏定輸?
win.
贏.
You took advantage of it so quickly, have you taken advantage of it?
咁快占好, 你有冇占呢?
Why are you angry with me?
你係咩氣我啊?
Dewei?
得未啊?
ok us
得了架我哋.
You got it.
你得啦.
Do you have to be careful?
你得咪得囉?
over things
過嘢.
Was it stolen? Was it beaten?
偷啦, 打過?
Not only?
唔但喇?
Let's buy something?
我哋買嘢啊?
Dedicated to Long Island?
定仰龍島啊?
Dead, dead, dead!
死啦死啦死啦!
Super nice.
超 尼啊.
Dead, dead.
死啦死啦.
Just now I thought I was in the shot...
頭 先我覺得我係有入鏡嘅.
The first situation was so confusing.
頭先個情況係好混亂啊.
There will be about 5-6 hands arriving, and the mark will be on the back.
大概有5-6隻手到, 後面面標 到.
The first hand, bang!
第一隻手, 嘭!
Then he dialed it away, then the second hand, then the glasses were gone, and then you can
跟住佢就撥開, 跟住第二隻手, 跟住眼鏡都冇埋喇, 跟住就可以
The third and fourth, finally got pulled like this.
第三 第四隻, 最後咁就俾人扯住 咗咁樣啊
I saw him without his glasses, because I saw, I saw your eye, looking up like that.
我見到佢冇咗眼鏡, 因為我見到, 我見到你隻眼, 咁樣望上嚟
Tongtong, why are you crying?
彤彤你做乜喊啊?
Why are you crying?
你做乜喊啊?
I want to touch there first, can I catch which one it is?
我想係手先摸嗰度, 可以捉到係邊 一個?
I may have a part, you guys do, can you.
我可能有份嘅, 你哋有, 得唔 住
I should have a share.
我應該有份嘅
Wow!
嘩!
Hey, hey, hey.
嗱嗱嗱嗱
I don't think the mistress has caught all of her eyes.
我覺得情婦未入晒一隻眼嘅
But yes, they have a line, he if...
但係有喎, 佢哋有一條線喇, 佢如果...
Wait, wow, this...actually...it's crazy just for this hand,
等下先, 嘩, 呢隻... 其實 ... 專為呢隻手係好癲喎,
You have white hair.
你扯住啲頭白喎
Actually, I felt a little bit of mosquito carrot just now.
其實頭先有少少蚊蘿蔔嘅感覺
Save you, save you want to come.
救你喇, 救你想嚟
This force of his, wow, you see, is very strong.
佢呢個力, 嘩, 你睇, 好勁
I don't have many eyes that are all red. Did I get beaten?
冇多隻眼係紅晒, 係咪俾人打 完?
I am already without glasses in this position.
我已經係冇咗眼鏡喇呢個位
Actually, he really... almost had an eye.
其實佢真係... 差啲一隻眼喎
If you pull up a little higher, I'll be in the frame.
你扯高多少少我就入到去喇
I think Mistress this her a little worse.
我覺得情婦呢個佢差少少嘅
He didn't, where, he didn't have a single eye.
佢 冇啦, 邊度啦, 佢冇一格眼 睛
Listen to me, because my eyes are really relatively small, actually into the sun in this eye.
聽我講, 因為我對眼真係比較細, 其實入曬喇呢隻眼睛
No, no, but you... your face is negatively curled, really.
唔係, 唔係, 但係你... 你 個面皮都係負皮捲嘅, 真係
Your carrots are taller.
你嘅蘿蔔扯高啲啊
What's the point of fighting and frightening each other?
一比一打和吓, 呢齣係咪?
It's time to make a shop, it's time to make a shop.
打鋪囉, 打鋪囉
I'm sorry, brother.
差少少啫, 副哥
Like those BB pictures in superstar waves.
好似超星波嗰啲BB圖咁
These tangerines are really out of the question.
真係出盡嚟呢啲木柑
I have another strategy, this time this is to say that fat mosquitoes dominate the position day and night first.
我又有策略, 今次呢就係話肥蚊日 夜霸位先
If the fat mosquito is let go, the three of us will pick it up like this underneath.
個肥蚊如果俾人蚊走, 我哋三個仔 喺下面咁樣攝上去
I want you to quickly occupy the front position.
我想你快啲霸前面嗰個位置
Look or not, Erzai, Go!
睇唔睇, 二仔, Go!
The Arts Bureau is over, wow, Chairman Chu is in a mess.
藝局完咗, 哇, 朱主席亂哂喎
Yes, it’s a great match.
係呀, 打場好大交
The fish is so stupid. How can I be the chairman?
條魚太咩哂喎, 點做主席啊?
What strategies did you have, you guys?
頭先你有啲咩策略啊, 你哋?
Just now, I was thinking of getting a broken shirt and hitting you alone.
頭先呢, 我係諗住攞件爛衫, 粒你一個人
Wow, your friend, the line is here.
嘩, 你條友, 線到
Hit until I realize, can not throw away.
打到我發覺, 甩唔到
So I donate from the back back to the front.
所以我喺後面捐返去前面
Our strategy is very simple.
我哋嘅策略呢, 好簡單
I was thinking that the fat mosquitoes rushed over, you would need three or four people to get away.
就諗住肥蚊衝過去呢, 你哋就要三 四個人先蚊得走去
Our three sons came up on top of the people patrol below.
我哋三個仔喺下面人巡頂上嚟
Why is it slow to enter?
點解入去慢咗?
There is no space left.
已經冇位
You can actually stretch with me, I'm so dumb.
其實陪我伸得, 我啞到個位
Then they kept choosing left, choosing a right ear so he looked and turned and went to the left ear.
跟住佢哋係咁係咁揀咗, 揀一隻右 耳咁佢睇轉頭就走去左耳
Pick again.
再揀過
Yes, I said why is his ear still there?
係呀, 我就話點解佢隻耳朵仲喺度 嘅?
Because I'm clearly driving on the left side.
因為我明明揸住左邊喇嘛
Because there are two of each.
因為有兩隻嘛每個人
Come on, come on, and choose photos, and take photos.
嚟喇嚟喇, 又有揀相, 又有相
Yes, yes.
有喇, 有喇.
Hello!
喂!
Wow!
哇!
Birth appearance?
生相?
What a handsome guy, G-5.
好靚仔呀G-5
He is really handsome.
真係好靚仔喎
We win.
我哋贏喇
But my mouth is filled with tears?
但係我個嘴都攞得分啦?
You brushed it into his ear hole?
你刷左入佢隻耳窿度啊?
Your finger is... Mia?
你個手指係... 係咪呀?
Very harsh, all of them.
好 狠喎, 全部都
See the nail, found it, which red nail, is it you?
睇到指甲呀, 搵到呀, 邊個紅色 指甲, 係咪你?
you.
你
There is evidence.
有證據喎
Wait a minute, and this one, you stir your hair again, look, sunburned hair,
等陣先, 同埋呢一個呢, 你地又 攪頭髮, 睇下, 赤曬個頭,
My hair is exposed to the sun, and my hair is exposed to mosquitoes. I want to ask, my hair is exposed to the sun, and my hair is exposed to mosquitoes.
赤曬個頭, 係咪又蚊頭髮先, 我想問, 頭髮又蚊起曬, 見到頭
The skin is already, I know my mouth will be so up, because it was pulled, I choose him down
皮 啦已經, 我知唔知我個嘴會咁 起, 因為俾人扯住咗, 我揀佢落
Come on, if no one pulls, my land will be stoned together.
嚟, 如果無人扯住, 我地會石埋 一齊添呀
Is there any stone in your land, right?
你地有冇石, 啱?
I just had stones to girls crying, do not know where to talk, three.
我頭先有石到女仔喊, 唔知邊講 嘢, 三個
Ok, so that means this game, one to one.
好, 咁即係今局呀, 一比一
So that means we have to get to the third set, the tiebreaker.
咁即係我地要到第三局, 決勝局囉 囉
OK.
好呀.
Get ready, the third game, the deciding game!
準備, 第三局, 決勝局!
GO!
GO!
Okay, three girls don't get angry with their hands, then they use their hands, I use... their feet,
咁得啦, 三個女仔不嬲用手吖嘛, 咁用手, 我地呢就用... 腳,
It's easy to stand up to it.
都好頂返住
I sprinkle my mouth wide and he doesn't dare to insert your hand and stick it out... stir
我地撒大個口佢咪唔敢插你手埋嚟 囉, 係咪都伸條舌出嚟... 攪
Hair, 3 2 1 just just just just just just just just just just
頭 髮喇, 3 2 1 啱啱啱啱 啱啱啱啱啱啱啱啱啱啱啱啱啱啱啱啱
Right just just just just just just just just just just just just just just just just just just just just just
啱 啱啱啱啱啱啱啱啱啱啱啱啱啱啱
Right just now I want to eat good.
啱 啱啱 我 想食好
Hey, working on it guys.
喂,搞緊啲喇大家
You have to let Poki walk out.
你要畀Poki行出嚟
You...you grab the left first the day before yesterday, and you grab the left first the day before yesterday.
你...你搶左前天先,搶左前天 先
The film is over, the film is over, the film is over.
影完,影完,影完
Wow, some saliva, we got there!
嘩,有啲口水,我哋走到呢!
I want to ask one thing, why did it become like this?
我想問一件事,點解會變成咁樣嘅?
Wow!
嘩!
When did you buy it, the rotten shirt?
你幾時買,件爛衫?
Are you buying it?
你買呀?
You can get it as soon as you enter!
入一入去就有!
Are there any black and yellow ones?
有冇啲黑色嘅黃色嘅?
Because my bridge is one fast, three two one ...
因為我條橋就係 一就快,三二一就 ...
The grains went down, and the grains fell away.
粒落去,一嘢粒咗
I wonder why your hands are placed like this, so strange?
我想問點解你哋啲手擺到咁樣嘅, 咁奇怪嘅?
Because someone licked our hands!
因為有人舔過我哋手啦!
I said really...I said that, because they love to cover us like that for six months,
我話真係... 我係頭先話, 因為佢哋好鍾意咁樣遮我哋半年,
Our trick is to ignore anything, just wipe big into your mouth and...
我哋個招式就係唔理任何嘢, 總之抹大落口就...
It means they really ignore me, they keep hitting me...
等於佢哋真係唔理我, 佢哋繼續撳 我...
Wow, so disgusting!
嘩,好噁心呀!
He also hit the right topic this time, it's you!
佢仲要撞正今次個題目呢, 係你 呀!
I was the one who licked that hand.
我係舔嗰隻手嘅
I don't know one either, I ignore it...
我都唔知一隻,我唔理佢...
Licking for a long time, are you sticking into my hand?
舔 咗 勁耐,你係咪黐入我嘅手?
Yes, these candies are being eaten somewhere, it turns out I don't know why I clicked, took my hand back into
係呀,呢啲糖係唔知邊度食緊囉, 原來我唔知點解撳撳下,拎返隻手成
...
...
I can eat sugar, I can eat sugar.
我 有食到糖嘅,我食到糖
Do you know the relationship between you and me?
你知定係你知?
I can eat some sugar, it's sweet.
我都係食到啲糖,係甜甜味囉
I don't know where it is.
我唔知係邊度啦
So why is it my hand?
咁點解係我隻手呢?
Wow!
嘩!
We finished filming!
我哋影完!
With some saliva we left!
有啲口水我哋走咗!
Then what did Ah Bing say in it?
跟住頭先阿冰喺裏面講咗咩?
I said my whole hand was covered with Brother J's saliva!
我話成隻手都係J哥啲口水!
No, what you said at the beginning was...
唔係呀,你一開始講嘅係...
My whole mouth is filled with Brother J's saliva!
我成個口都係J哥啲口水!
The whole mouth is filled with Brother J's saliva!
成個口都係J哥啲口水!
ha!
哈!
嗱!
嗱!
They beat Kellen.
佢哋打Kellen喇.
is that so
係咪咁?
Small debate on the spot: Should middle school students hit Kellen?
即場小辯論,中學生應否打K ellen?
It shouldn't be, I just said it wrong everyone...
係唔應該,啱啱講錯咗呀大家.
Is there really any?
係咪真係有呀?
I don't stop.
我唔停頓喇.
Immediately, when are you willing to wipe your hands?
即刻,你哋幾時肯抹手呢?
I really want to know if I made it...
我真係想知我有冇入到鏡.
Yes.
有呀.
My tongue is so out...
我條舌好出喎.
The tongue is tied in the shape of a heart.
條舌係心形添呀.
Tong Tong forgot about her new tongue...
彤彤唔記得新舌喎.
Did I have, I was beaten...
係咪我有,我俾人打咗下.
Hit him, he's screaming...
打佢,佢係尖叫緊喇.
This tongue should be responsive.
呢條舌應該係利應嘅.
Hey, look clearly.
喂,睇清楚啲.
Li Ying's.
利應嘅.
The profit shouldn't be that high...
利應邊有咁高呀.
Is this plan beneficial?
呢個計有利咩?
Even who
就算係邊個.
Advantageous location.
有利位置.
Because the eight of us couldn't reach a consensus in the end...
因為我哋八個最後都達成唔到共識.
We decided to get the staff outside the venue to help us see...
我哋決定搵場外嘅工作人員幫我哋 睇.
They are convinced that Leigh.
佢哋確信係利.
Only tie one tongue.
只係一條舌頭.
Just don't know whose tongue...
只係唔知哪位嘅舌頭.
But luckily, we have installed a CCTV inside...
但係好彩,我哋喺裏面已經安咗個閉 路電視.
So we now go to the video right away and we can know who...
咁 我 哋而家即刻去睇片, 就可以知邊個喇.
Benefit.
利益.
The benefits are below.
利益喺下面喇.
yes i am
係呀,我嚟.
There are so high over there...
個邊有咁高呀.
You guys won the game, lost the wind.
你哋贏咗遊戲,輸咗風度.
But you lose the game, lose the honesty.
但係你哋輸咗遊戲,輸埋誠實度.
You guys lost girls.
你哋輸咗女孩.
All you get is our saliva.
你哋得到嘅只有我哋啲口水.
So this game was won by our boys' school boys...
所以呢局遊戲都係我哋男校男生勝出 嘅.
Boys in a boys' school.
男校男生.
although we
雖然我哋...
Maybe lost some games...
可能輸咗啲遊戲喇.
But I was playing with three girls...
但係我係同三個女仔玩嘅.
we are all
我哋都係咗.
You were playing with three girls, four boys...
頭先呢你同三個女仔玩,係四個男仔 玩.
I'm so happy.
係咪我幾開心呀.
Enter the next game immediately.
即刻進入下個遊戲.
Top cup battle.
頂杯戰.
Each team sends two members at a time.
每隊每次派出兩位成員.
Everyone holds a plastic cup on their head.
各人頭上頂住膠杯.
Players have to try to drop the plastic cup of the opposing team...
玩家要設法將對面隊嘅膠杯整跌.
While keeping your own plastic cup from falling...
同時要保持住自己嘅膠杯唔跌.
The team that ended up holding the plastic cup on the field.
最後喺場上頂住膠杯嘅隊伍.
Win for it.
為 之勝出.
There's no way, the strongest of the other party must be the pig's mic...
冇計,對方最勁一定係豬咪喇.
Both have strong athletic ability.
運動能力都強.
And the height is yours to fight against.
同埋個身高係你去對抗喇.
Then you are very advantageous...
咁你係好有優勢喎.
people can't see you
啲人係見唔到你嘛.
Send him up first...
派起佢先.
I want to hit John.
我要打阿John.
Most importantly no expression.
最重要冇表情.
Ha ha ha ha.
哈哈哈哈.
One is tall and one is short.
一高一矮.
withstand.
頂住.
to scare him
嚇佢.
Follow me and raise your hands behind you.
跟 住呢後面手長抬.
You try it out.
你試玩.
He's afraid of his uncle...
佢驚阿叔呀.
so fight.
咁打.
Will make up for it later.
後面再補位.
done.
搞掂.
no good thing
唔好事.
好啊。
OK喎.
saved
救到喎.
can you guys jump up
你哋可唔可以跳起呀.
You jump up and fight like that...
你跳起咁樣打.
Jump up I don't think hard brother...
跳起我咪諗硬喎師兄.
Baby I'll try to jump up now...
Baby我而家試下跳起.
Try jumping.
你試下跳喇.
One trick to go long.
做多一隻絕招.
ah.
啊.
Wow.
嘩.
We now soldiers try to use a trick...
我哋而家阿兵試下用個計.
Hold a cup first.
攞住個杯先.
Don't be seen by the opposite side...
唔好畀對面見到.
Block, block, block.
擋住擋住擋住.
Ha ha ha ha.
哈哈哈哈.
Turn around and see...
轉個圈嚟睇下.
By the way we have to fight... and bow our heads...
話說我哋要打... 又低頭喎.
So exciting.
好勁.
Go in and actually.
入去其實.
Put the food in with a whip.
食埋條鞭入去喇.
i have to
我要咁樣囉.
It's the brother in the ear...
係耳邊嘅師兄.
this is our
呢 個係我哋嘅...
Big chicken.
大雞.
And we can make it longer.
同埋我哋可以整耐啲.
Let's get a Gel.
我哋攞個Gel嘛.
Then we can press the camp.
咁我哋可以壓個營.
You have to say that we are really good students...
你要話我哋真係乖學生喎.
We are just Nerds.
我哋Nerd咋.
We bad.
我哋壞.
We Gel head.
我哋Gel頭.
we are not Lut
我哋唔係Lut.
So you look over.
咁你望過嚟.
Hey, take a look first.
喂你睇下先.
you don't have to
你唔使嘅.
Everyone is so tight...
大家咁緊.
I hear your strategy.
我聽到哂你哋嘅策略喇.
What did they say?
佢哋講咩呀?
I don't know.
唔知喎.
Heard it.
聽到啦.
I heard it.
聽到哂啦.
What a waste.
好廢呀.
The elites on both sides of you have stood up...
你 哋 兩邊嘅人馬精英已經企咗 出去喇.
hey lost
喂輸咗.
lost.
輸咗.
We need so Plan A first.
我哋要咁Plan A先.
OK?
OK?
good.
好.
hey listen to me
喂聽我講嘢.
Be prepared.
好準備.
3 2 1.
3 2 1.
start.
開始.
I suspect we hit badly...
我懷疑我哋撞差啦.
We crashed...
我哋撞咗差喇.
Ah Tongtong.
呀童童.
The hero saw Tongtong.
英雄所見啦童童.
Fat mosquito.
肥蚊.
Go.
Go.
Come over quickly...
快點走過嚟喇.
Fat mosquito.
肥蚊.
Let's disperse Miss...
我哋散開小姐喇.
Tony.
Tony.
Blue shrimp boys.
藍蝦男生.
Why is the head so cheap?
點樣個頭咁平呢?
You think we are vegetarians...
你當我哋呢食齋嘅.
none.
無.
nothing
無嘢喎.
It's a bird's nest.
係鳥巢呀.
I’ll touch my head quickly today decía temmeuchg
我今日快先摸下個頭 deca temmeuchg
Andrew.
Andrew.
great.
好 嘢.
Our blue shrimp boys took down the first battle...
我哋藍蝦男生取下第一戰.
Come the second round.
嚟到第二回合.
Nanhe girls sent Golden King Naixing Xian to take photos.
南河女生派出 Golden King 凴星鮮忙拍啦.
Who is a girl? May I ask?
誰係女生,請問?
and the Apipe Orchestra.
同埋阿管樂團
You guys are not the strongest, we have always been strong.
你哋唔係最勁,我哋一向勁
Oh sorry, yes, you guys are the strongest.
噢 sorry,係,你哋最勁
I hit the left second force.
我劈左第二勁
I suspect Fan Coffin opposite.
我懷疑對面範棺
Why doesn't your head fall so tilted?
點解你個頭斜到咁都唔跌?
But he put it on his head too... I suspect he used glue.
但佢都放喺頭上面喎... 我懷 疑佢用咗膠水呀
His head shape is like this.
佢個頭型係咁喎
It's horizontal!
佢打橫咗呀!
Yes, you are spicy!
係啦,你辣喎!
Shit glue?
屎屎膠水呀?
You really use a plugin right this?
您真係用個外掛喎呢個?
That Nagasaki guy just over there, he locked the plate tightly with that electric method of his.
啱啱嗰邊嗰個長崎佬呀, 佢都係用 佢嗰個電法鎖緊咗個盤
That’s it, you’re dead material Chao Lao.
係囉,死料巢佬
Get ready, 3, 2, 1, start!
準備吓,3,2,1,開始!
Listen to me.
聽妹
Let's not play by ourselves, can we live?
唔好自己玩啦我哋,得唔得住?
That's how we look besides the collision?
撞住之外我哋都係咁樣吓?
Li Ying, what are you doing, Li Ying?
黎英你搞乜呀黎英?
Hey, spread some, spread some!
喂,擴散啲,擴散啲!
Diffuse d is left and right, left and right clamp attack!
擴散啲係左右,左右夾攻!
Catch me!
捉住我!
Yeah!
Yeah!
Ten times the buckle!
十倍引扣!
I'm stuck with him, I'm stuck with him!
我同佢黐手,我同佢黐手!
stick!
黐!
Oops, lost!
哎呀,輸咗喇!
The whole cup was taken!
整個杯攞咗呀!
You did a great job!
你做得好好!
Well done, our strategy worked!
做得好好,我哋嘅策略成功!
Student Union is really sorry, our boys' school boys won again.
學生會真係唔好意思啦,我哋男校男 生又贏多次啦
I have to be sorry.
唔得唔好意思
That battle was actually quite good, because, as soon as I saw the soldier's expression from the beginning,
啱嗰場戰鬥其實幾好睇嘅,因為呢, 一見到阿兵嗰個表情由一開始,
That look full of confidence to fall into this abyss.
嗰個充滿自信去到跌入呢個深淵嘅嗰 個樣啦
He thought he won hard.
佢以為自己贏硬
He will never be happy again.
佢以後再唔康樂啦
Wow, I got a lot just now.
嘩,頭先得到咗好多呀
what do you get
你得到啲咩呀?
He was intertwined with me just now.
頭先佢同我十指緊扣呀
Yes, really!
係呀,真係呀!
Just now, oops, he stuck followed by ten fingers clasped, he didn't die to let go.
頭先,哎呀,佢黐咗跟住十指緊扣, 佢唔死得放手啦
Yes, he hit me with one hand.
係呀,佢同我一手撞咗我呀
Play till the end!
玩到鋪!
Although I won’t argue with my teammates...
雖然隊友呢鋪我都唔爭...
You are not good, I think you.
你好唔得喎,我覺得你
No, strategy, right?
唔係呀,策略呀嘛,唔係咩?
Which hand are you using to clasp his fingers tightly?
你係用邊隻手同佢十指緊扣呀?
He hit this hand of mine!
佢撞咗我呢隻手呀!
Dan Jie is happy.
彈劫都開心
Since that's the case, let's move on to the next game and win us one more round.
既然係咁,我哋快啲進入下個 game, 又贏多我哋一鋪啦,
good?
好?
good!
好!
OK!
好呀!
OK, let’s go to the next game immediately!
好,馬上進入下個game!
Wow!
嘩!
Qi Zhanqiu PLUS Balance Challenge Each team sends two people to compete in Qi Zhanqiu duel.
氣展球PLUS平衡力挑戰 每隊派 出兩人進行氣展球對決, 兩人進行
Balance challenge.
平 衡力挑戰
Participants in the balance challenge will need to bite into a snow stick with their mouths, and a coloring will be placed on it.
平衡力挑戰嘅參賽者需要用口咬住雪 條棍, 而雪條棍上面會放置色仔
If the contestant who performs the air show successfully scores a goal, he or she can add a color to the opposite team.
假如進行氣展球嘅參賽者成功入球, 就可以加一粒色仔去到對面隊
When the color boy falls, the contestant will be eliminated.
當 色仔跌落嚟,該參賽者就會被淘 汰
When all participants who performed the Balance Challenge are eliminated, the game ends and the winning team gets
所有進行平衡力挑戰嘅參賽者都被淘 汰嘅時候, 遊戲結束,勝出隊伍得
1 point.
1 分
Note that only the red large air balloons will be considered valid first, and other small air balloons will be considered interference.
注意,只有紅色大氣展球先會視作有 效, 其他小氣展球為干擾,
Instant goals are not counted.
即使入球都不作計算
Wow!
嘩!
Lots of cams this time.
好多部cam我哋今次
That’s right!
無錯呀!
On to the last game, which is this...
進入最後一個遊戲啦,就係呢個 ...
Air Ball Balancing Contest!
氣展球平衡大賽!
That’s right!
無錯呀!
Another name for this is they play us suffer!
呢個另一個名叫做 佢哋玩我哋受 呀!
OK!
OK!
Come on!
嚟啦喎!
Two brothers!
兩位兄弟!
I haven’t played enough to live!
嚟呀!
What?
咩呀?
Why?
點解呀?
My cover is on his side!
我個蓋係佢嗰邊呀!
Your brothers just gave it to us!
啱啱你啲兄弟送俾我哋嘅呀!
What?
咩 呀?
You gave it to others yourself?
你自己畀人嘅?
Because just called us, you guys try to see if you can fly to the other side one!
因為頭先叫我哋,你哋試下可唔可以 一個飛去對面呀!
That's it just now, flying like this...
頭先咪就係咁囉,飛咁...
Have they all been tricked?
佢哋中晒未人計呀!
We don't have one now!
我哋而家一個都冇喇!
You look at our faces, do we find it interesting?
你望我哋個樣,我哋有冇覺得好有趣 呀?
Yes!
有喎!
I think there is!
我覺得有喎!
You try to stand in our place, it's easy to hold things!
你試下企我哋呢個位,好易拿嘢!
So we're the ones with the best teeth on this side, Tiger Talk!
咁我哋呢邊就係牙力最好嘅人, 虎言樂團!
The Chess Society of Export Technique!
出口術嘅象棋學會!
Chairman Chu who is singing the song!
唱開歌嘅朱主席!
I'm the singer-songwriter Peng Ka-lai-ying!
我係唱開歌嘅彭嘉麗英!
Hey, let’s sing back now!
喂,即刻唱返首嚟啫!
It turned out that he left voluntarily!
原來自願走!
Hey, what a different song!
喂,唔同歌嘅!
Heavy!
重磅!
The war is about to break out!
大戰一觸即發!
Hey, stop it for me!
喂,幫我攔下!
Wow!
嘩!
got it!
有咗!
Hello!
喂!
It’s time to eat!
食色啦!
Eh!
欸!
Food-colored Katsuya!
食色勝也!
Ouch!
哎喲!
They can't talk!
佢哋冇得講嘢啦!
Bite things!
咬住嘢!
I'm here again!
我再喺!
in!
喺!
Right slash?
對個斜線?
I'm not surprised!
我唔驚!
straight line!
直線!
Hello!
喂!
The lover's pants have lost color!
情人褲跌咗粒色喇!
The lover's pants have been burned!
情人褲已經燒咗喇!
So it's just hair makeup!
所以就係得發妝!
Great!
好喇!
Just got the news!
啱收到消息!
Now they haven't signed a petition here saying they want to add color!
而 家佢哋呢邊未聯署話要加色喇!
Pine sun!
鬆晒!
You are a little scared!
你有少少斜吓!
You have a little tilt downward!
你有少少斜向下!
Be careful!
小心吓!
Hello!
喂!
You have arrived!
你到嚟喇!
Stop it!
要撲住!
ah!
啊!
Good shake!
快啲gut shake!
You two gut shake quickly!
你哋兩個快啲gut shake!
What a smile on his part!
佢有乜嘢笑啊!
come on hurry up!
快啲啦!
Hello!
喂!
Let's play Lucky is not good?
不如我哋玩Lucky係唔好?
no ah!
冇啊!
Come on, come on!
嚟嚟嚟嚟!
Come on!
嚟呀!
Hello!
喂!
ah!
啊!
Wow!
嘩!
He uses his hands!
佢用手啊!
Palm!
手 板啊!
Ghost phone ball!
鬼影電話球!
Wow!
嘩!
You hit it!
你打到!
What a taste!
有乜味!
Hold on!
頂住啊!
My teammates!
我嘅隊友!
Give some!
畀啲!
Pressure him!
壓力佢地!
I'm stressed!
自己壓力!
Add more color!
再加色!
I asked Sinnie, where did she appreciate us the most on the way back?
我問阿Sinnie呢,佢最欣賞我 哋返路黎邊過呀?
Sinnie, I don’t want you to see me as a friend?
Sinnie我唔想你唔想見到自己 一個朋友呀?
What did you admire most about me?
你最欣賞過我?
no!
唔係啊!
I'm a ghost!
我係幽靈!
What's going on?
咩事呀?
Hey Apple!
Hey Apple!
Hi Ami!
Hi Ami!
Yeah yeah yeah yeah!
呀 呀呀呀呀呀!
Wow!
嘩!
Ah Sinnie hits!
阿Sinnie打出!
Don't think about it!
唔好想!
Oh shit!
噢Shit!
I have some rulers!
我有啲尺!
Some rulers!
有啲尺!
Come on!
加油啊!
withstand!
頂住!
No Sinnie wants to use her hands?
唔係阿Sinnie想用手?
will it
會唔會?
Hurry up!
快啲啊!
Lai Ying!
賴英!
OK!
係囉!
Carrying the body and mind to death!
背死身心!
Those balls will make it move!
嗰啲波波會令到佢走位!
How many pills?
幾多粒啊?
Five pills!
五粒!
Top position!
頂位!
three...four...
三...四...
Seven pills!
七粒啊!
Add two more!
加兩粒啊!
Come on!
加油啊!
Yeah!
Yeah!
withstand!
頂住!
Talk about it!
講下嘢啊!
He doesn't recognize you!
佢認唔到你!
Lai Ying!
賴英!
so tired!
好累啊!
It doesn't matter!
唔緊要!
You are very strong!
你好勁喇!
Seven pills!
七粒!
We finally win!
我地贏啦終於!
Hard work!
勁辛苦!
It can't be chewed, but the throat is still still!
都 冇得督仲喉嚨定!
oh really?
真係?
Tie!
係!
Already in the throat at the beginning!
一開波已經督仲喺喉嚨定!
As soon as it’s tied, it’s a bust!
即 係就嘩!
Good luck!
好吉!
Then I want to cut!
然後想cut啦!
Then cut can not, slowly spray back the tongue out!
然後cut唔到,慢慢噴返條舌出 嚟!
That means there's still a whole pocket of saliva in there!
即係仲有成兜口水喺度呢!
Then can't get out the tongue, and can't swallow!
然後出唔到舌,又吞唔到!
I'm sorry!
唔好意思啊!
The two with the worst concentration in my land!
我地定力最差嗰兩個!
But I’ll do my best!
但我地盡左力!
really!
真係!
Popular support!
民心!
Let the people do their best!
民心盡左力!
The strength of our gang defeated you!
我地一幫實力打低你!
It’s hard to hold back your laughter!
忍住笑勁辛苦!
It's hard to hear whether there is anything to say!
聽成有冇講嘢勁辛苦!
Wow!
嘩!
So noisy!
好嘈啊!
become!
成!
Your land wins student union!
你地贏嘅學生會!
OK!
OK!
You really win!
真 係你贏!
good!
好!
Our land immediately enters the scoring ring battle!
我地即刻進入計分環戰!
Tie!
係!
Let’s play the game!
遊戲就玩哂啦!
Big win!
大獲!
Is it a microphone this time?
今次係咪啊?
Our land has won a great victory!
我地大獲全勝啊!
Then you're just playing!
咁咪你地係玩囉!
Go catch chess!
去捉象棋啦!
Dropped into the park!
落公園啦!
King of Riders!
騎利王!
Just catch...King Li!
個仔捉...騎利王!
Click on the student union?
點啊學生會?
Are you having fun?
玩得開唔開心啊?
Aren't you happy to lose?
輸得開唔開心啊?
I am so passionate!
我地好熱血啊!
We are all doing our best!
我地都盡左力!
My land is doing well!
我地好好啊!
Our country will have no regrets!
我地國將無悔!
Are you a college student?
大學生嚟?
Your place?
你地?
OK!
係囉!
Let’s rise soon!
就快升囉!
In short, this time is our land wins all!
總之呢今次就係我地贏晒啦!
Blue school blue students!
藍校藍生!
So our land is going to have rewards in the section!
所以我地係將會有獎勵嘅環節嘅!
Can we play with him again?
係咪可以同佢地再玩啊?
Similar!
類似啦!
Then my land will receive a big bag of Namco tokens!
咁我地就會獲得一大袋嘅Namco 代幣!
We will play throwing rainbows!
我地會玩掟彩虹!
And your land lost this have to work as a staff to S ERVE my land!
而你地輸咗嘅呢就要做工作人員去S ERVE我地!
Hello everyone!
大家好!
My local student union!
我地係學生會!
Welcome to all the winners to play rainbow throwing at Namco!
歡迎各位贏家嚟到Namco玩掟彩 虹啊!
The gameplay is quite simple!
玩法相當簡單啊!
Just toss the gold coin!
只要將金幣輕輕一拋!
If you don’t fall into the pit, don’t hit the bay, and don’t hit the white color, you’ll get a prize!
唔落坑,唔雜灣,唔中白色呢就有獎 品啦!
And my prize is very rich!
而我地個獎品非常豐富啊!
There is something to play with, something to eat and something practical!
玩嘅又有,食嘅又有,實用嘅都有!
Let's see if you can win a prize!
睇下你地可唔可以贏到獎品啦!
Win the big prize!
贏大獎喎!
Win big prize!
贏大獎啦!
Let me show you off!
攞晒你囉!
Hey hey hey hey!
喂喂喂喂喂!
Really sorry!
真係唔好意思!
Yes!
係呀!
come on!
加油!
It's some buckles!
係啲支扣啊!
Wait first!
等先!
My land is stopped first, okay?
我地停定咗先嘅,好唔好?
OK, OK!
好呀好呀!
Just a short distance away from winning the grand prize!
差少少就贏到大獎啦!
Come on!
加油啊!
Hello!
喂!
Why don't we throw rainbows!
不如我地唔好掟彩虹囉!
Throw someone!
掟人囉!
Hello!
喂!
Look over there!
你睇下嗰邊!
well!
唉!
Sorry!
Sorry!
Finally got something to play!
終於有得玩啦!
Hello!
喂!
What magnifying glass do you need?
使咩放大鏡睇睇?
No need!
唔使啦!
I can see it!
我地睇到喎!
Tie it up!
紮彎啊!
Yes!
係呀!
What a middle ground!
好中間啊!
Congratulations!
恭喜晒!
Miss!
唔中啊!
The red one!
紅色嗰個!
Yes!
係呀!
watching television!
睇電視!
Hello!
喂!
Miss!
唔中!
No!
唔係!
First of all, I didn't win yet!
首先頭先仲唔中先!
You think so!
你地平心而論!
Miss!
唔中!
good!
好!
If you don’t hit it, I’ll believe you!
唔中就信你地!
Miss!
唔中!
Come on!
得啦!
see...
睇...
well!
唉!
Right now, right?
而家中咗係咪啊?
Hello!
喂!
have!
有!
Yes!
係 呀!
Win!
贏呀!
Hello!
喂!
That's enough for you!
你夠囉!
Yes!
係呀!
Sorry!
不好意思呀!
Everyone missed it!
大家唔中呀!
Come on next time!
下次加油!
Hello!
喂!
Purple!
紫色!
sincere!
真心!
Take a look!
望一望!
Hello!
喂!
I won!
中咗喎!
Hit!
中呀!
OK!
OK呀!
So handsome!
好帥!
There is one!
有呢一個!
This is so right!
呢個好正呀!
I want!
我要!
Congratulations!
恭喜晒!
Get off him!
落佢地啦!
Hello!
喂!
green!
綠色!
Green seems to be really right!
綠色好似真係中!
Hello!
喂!
Medium green!
中綠色呀!
Green Please choose the gift there!
綠色請揀嗰度嘅禮物呀!
I found that this person and I are always out of bounds!
我發現呢位同我成日都出界喎!
Really right!
真係中!
That one!
呢個!
That yellow one!
呢個黃色!
Hit!
中呀!
I'll give you a private!
我私人畀個撈撈你!
So we had so much fun to thank our sponsor NAMCO this time!
咁我哋玩得咁開心都要多謝返我哋今 次嘅贊助商NAMCO嘅!
Thank you NAMCO!
多謝NAMCO!
Hong Kong NAMCO is a Japanese direct-operated company!
香港NAMCO係日本直營公司!
There are many Japanese latest and Japanese latest!
有好多日本最新同埋日本最新!
Japanese gift dolls!
日本嘅景品公仔!
There are also many different game consoles to experience!
亦都有好多唔同嘅遊戲機可以體驗!
In recent years, Japanese-themed rides have been introduced!
近年仲引入咗日本主題遊樂設施!
Perfect for a family to bring children to play!
啱晒一家帶細個嚟玩!
If you like Japan, remember to come to NAMCO!
鍾意日本嘅大家記住嚟NAMCO玩 呀!
Come to NAMCO to play and solve maths!
嚟NAMCO玩同解數!
good!
好!
Remember CLSS after watching the video!
睇完片記得CLSS!
Comment!
Comment!
Like!
Like!
Share!
Share!
Subscribe!
Subscribe!
OK!
OK!
SUGA PARTY GAME!
SUGA PARTY GAME!
I want to kill you!
要掛你啫!
SUGA!
SUGA!
Do you want to miss me bye bye?
要掛我拜拜?
No need!
唔使啦!
Bye-Bye!
拜拜!